<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<content>

    <section>
        <title>Art Of Money</title>
        <id>refArtOfMoney</id>
        <img>
            /sites/CulminatingTGJ2O/pages/gallery/photoshop/include/Pu_ArtOfMoney.jpg
        </img>
        <alt>Art Of Money</alt>
        <class></class>
        <expand></expand>
        <software>Adobe Photoshop CS4</software>
        <text>
            This piece of work is an example banknote of a fictitious currency. The background depicts a circuit board-like design along with the silhouette of a city or the solar system. A picture of the sun as well as the globe and an atom are included on the
            bill as watermarks. The foreground picture on front and back of the bill is Bill Nye the Science Guy and a chimpanzee, respectively. All of these images are related to the overall science theme of this bill. Three skills I gained while completing
            this project were cropping irregularly shaped images, changing the opacity of images, and manipulating the colour tone of images. Two skills I would like to strengthen are the ability of incorporate a cohesive colour scheme as well as intricate
            background designs.
        </text>
    </section>

    <section>
        <title>Asian Heritage Poster</title>
        <id>refAsianHeritage</id>
        <img>
            /sites/CulminatingTGJ2O/pages/gallery/photoshop/include/PuM_AsianHeritagePoster.jpg
        </img>
        <alt>Asian Heritage</alt>
        <class></class>
        <expand></expand>
        <software>Adobe Photoshop CS4</software>
        <text>
            This piece of work is a poster to raise awareness on the subject of Asian Heritage month. It features various symbols associated with culture in different parts of Asia as well as Canada. Animals found in Asia, such as the panda, tigers, elephants as well as plants such as bamboo and the lotus are shown on the poster. Additionally, food associated with Asia, such as sushi as well as symbols associated with Asian culture, such as dragons, are incorporated into the poster. Three skills I gained while completing this project were cropping the background out of an image, positioning images, and developing an overall colour scheme. Two skills I would like to strengthen or learn are how to use banners and shapes on a poster and arranging text and images into a more visually appealing layout.
        </text>
    </section>

    <section>
        <title>Magazine Cover</title>
        <id>refMagazineCover</id>
        <img>
            /sites/CulminatingTGJ2O/pages/gallery/indesign/include/Pu_MagazineCover.jpg
        </img>
        <alt>Magazine Cover</alt>
        <class></class>
        <expand></expand>
        <software>Adobe InDesign CS4</software>
        <text>
            This piece of work is a replica of the cover of the National Geographic magazine published in June 2013. It features a diver in a wet suit in front of a underwater background on the ocean floor. Two headlights of a submarine can be seen in the background. Additionally, various pieces of text can be found on the cover, including the title, headings, subtitles, and captions. Three skills I gained while completing this project were cropping out the background of an image, changing the hue of images, and adding shapes to an image. Two skills I would like to strengthen or learn are the ability to identify a font by its appearance and adjusting the colour scheme of an image.
        </text>
    </section>

    <section>
        <title>Two Page Spread</title>
        <id>refTwoPageSpread</id>
        <img>
            /sites/CulminatingTGJ2O/pages/gallery/indesign/include/Pu_2PgSpread.jpg
        </img>
        <alt>2 Page Spread</alt>
        <class></class>
        <expand></expand>
        <software>Adobe InDesign CS4</software>
        <text>
            This piece of work is a replica of a two page spread found in a National Geographic magazine with the title of “The Long Shadow of Chernobyl”. It a large title a bit above the centre of the first page along with a bold subtitle underneath. The author and photographers are indicated below the subtitle and are followed by the text of the article. On the second page, an image of the rusted control room of the Chernobyl nuclear reactors can be seen with a caption underneath. Three skills I gained while completing this project were positioning text, selecting an appropriate font, and resizing images. Two skills I would like to strengthen or learn are the ability to identify a font by its appearance and aligning text boxes on a page.
        </text>
    </section>

    <section>
        <title>Stop Motion Animation</title>
        <id>refStopMotion</id>
        <img>
            /sites/CulminatingTGJ2O/pages/gallery/video/include/stopMotionScreenshot.jpg
        </img>
        <alt>Stop Motion Animation</alt>
        <class></class>
        <expand>/sites/CulminatingTGJ2O/pages/gallery/video/include/stopMotion2.mp4</expand>
        <software>Microsoft Movie Maker 2012</software>
        <text>
            This piece of work is a two minute stop motion animation. It explores the world at various scales, starting off with planets and zooming in until it reaches a microscopic level. It starts off with a view of planets, then zooms in to show the Earth, a city, a person, the skin of the person, and then the microorganisms inside the blood vessels in the skin. A storyboard was used during the preparation and filming stages of this project. Three skills I gained while completing this project were creating a video out of multiple images, adding sound effects to a video, and adding background music to a video. Two skills I would like to strengthen or learn are stabilizing a camera when filming and adding visual effects to a video.
        </text>
    </section>

</content>
