<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<content>

    <section>
        <title>Research Portfolio #1</title>
        <id>resPor1</id>
        <img>
            include/hihayk.png
        </img>
        <alt>Screenshot of http://www.hihayk.com/</alt>
        <class></class>
        <link>http://www.hihayk.com/</link>
        <text>
            This portfolio was created by hayk, an self-taught designer and coder. Something I like about this portfolio is its simplistic design and cohesive colour scheme. The web page is designed with short lines of text as well as simple graphics, which are very effective in conveying his ideas. The overall grey colour scheme with a tint of teal is quite visually appealing. I incorporated these into my portfolio by including as little text as necessary, and where long chunks of text are needed, the text is arranged into a visually appealing manner. My webpage features a dark grey and blue colour scheme with a bit of green in an attempt to match the simple colour scheme in this portfolio.
        </text>
    </section>

    <section>
        <title>Research Portfolio #2</title>
        <id>resPor2</id>
        <img>
            include/ryanscherf.png
        </img>
        <alt>Screenshot of http://ryanscherf.net/</alt>
        <class></class>
        <link>http://ryanscherf.net/</link>
        <text>
            This portfolio was created by Ryan Scherf, a digital designer. Something I like about this portfolio is its modular design used to display his projects. The web page is designed with rectangles with shadows arranged rows and columns, each encasing one project. The shadow and rectangles give the webpage an overall materialistic feel, as stated on the Google Material Design Guidelines. I incorporated this feature into my portfolio by using a similar material layout to arrange my projects. My webpage features a grey rectangles with shadows which darken if you hover over them arranged in a grid-like fashion, each encasing one of my projects.
        </text>
    </section>

    <section>
        <title>Research Portfolio #3</title>
        <id>resPor3</id>
        <img>
            include/jakobdeboer.png
        </img>
        <alt>Screenshot of http://jakobdeboer.com/work/</alt>
        <class></class>
        <link>http://jakobdeboer.com/work/</link>
        <text>
            This portfolio was created by Jackob De Boer, a digital designer and photographer. Something I like about this portfolio is the way the projects are arranged. The web page is designed with rectangles arranged rows and columns, each representing one project or image. If you click on one of the images, it expands, giving the viewed a large view of the image. The viewer can easily switch between this magnified view and the normal view simply by clicking outside the image. I incorporated this feature into my portfolio by using a similar layout to arrange my projects. On my webpage, if you click on the image of one of my projects, it will expand to fill up the entire screen, giving the viewer a better view of the image.
        </text>
    </section>

</content>
